-Oh! Hey, Rach! -Hi.
-嗨，瑞秋 -嗨
-Happy Valentine's Day! -You too!
-情人節快樂 -你也是
How's living at Ross'?
跟羅斯住的感覺如何？
It's good, except he makes us watch the Discovery Channel all day long.
很不錯，只不過他逼我們 整天看探索頻道
Something really boring happened to someone ugly in the Middle Ages.
一個在中世紀的醜八怪 發生了一件很無聊的事
Oh, thank you. I'll see you guys later.
謝謝 待會見
That is one lucky to-go cup of coffee.
那是一杯幸運的外帶咖啡
I wish you would get over her. I hate seeing you like this.
我希望你能忘了她 我討厭看到你這個樣子
Is there anything I can do for you? Do you wanna look down my top?
有什麼我能幫上忙的嗎？ 你要看看我的胸部嗎？
Thanks. Maybe later.
謝謝，或許待會再說吧
-Gunther, can I get a scone? -Want anything?
-阿甘，我能吃餅乾嗎？ -你要什麼？
I want a lot of things.
我要很多東西
I wanna be with the woman I love on Valentine's Day.
我希望跟我愛的女人 共度情人節
I want her to love me back.
我希望她也愛我
And I want relief from the wrenching pain of knowing that won't happen!
我希望能忘記 無法滿足渴望的悲傷
We have red bagels.
我們有紅色貝果
Okay.
好吧
The One With The Birthing Video
本集播出：生產錄影帶
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
So how do you guys like living together so far?
你們一起住 到目前為止還好吧？
-Oh, it's been good. -Yeah.
-很不錯 -對
Except Ross is more uptight about crumbs than you are.
只不過羅斯比你更在乎餅乾碎屑
There was a drumstick in the couch.
沙發上有根雞腿
And I am not uptight about crumbs.
我不在乎餅乾碎屑
It's just that, you know..
只不過…
crumbs attract mice. And mice leave droppings.
餅乾碎屑會引來老鼠 老鼠會隨地大便
And that's how the plague started.
黑死病就是那樣傳染開的
So you wanna relive that again..
如果你希望那種事再發生…
Mice didn't start the plague.
老鼠不會散佈黑死病
Rats did.
是野鼠才會
Rattus norvegicus, to be exact.
正確地來說是有病菌的野鼠
Oh, good God, Ross.
天啊，羅斯
Nick at Nite, once in a while.
偶爾讓我們看點卡通
All right, I'm going. Bye.
好吧，我要走了 再見
Phoebe, will you wait here?
菲比，能在這裡等一下嗎？
-I wanna get your opinion on something. -Yeah.
-我想聽聽你的意見 -好的
How does Mona feel about Rachel moving in?
蒙娜對瑞秋搬過去 有什麼看法？
I'm on my way to tell her.
我正要告訴她
She's been away all week, but she'll be cool.
她一整個星期都不在 但她會接受的
She's been so supportive.
她一直都很支持我
She even got the baby a T-shirt that says "Fossils are my friends."
她甚至幫寶寶買了 寫著「化石是我朋友」的上衣
Come on, Mona. Don't kiss ass.
少來了，蒙娜，別拍馬屁
So I'm gonna take off.
我得走了
Oh, shoot! Oh, shoot! Rachel wanted to see this tape.
快點 瑞秋想看這卷錄影帶
-What is it? -My friend giving birth.
-那是什麼？ -我朋友生孩子的錄影帶
Could you take it to your apartment?
你能把它帶回家嗎？
"Candy and Cookie"?
「糖果跟餅乾」？
Candy's the mom, Cookie's the daughter.
糖果是媽媽 餅乾是女兒
The father's name is also Cookie.
她爸爸也叫餅乾
Why am I friends with these people?
為什麼我會跟這些人做朋友？
Phoebe, come here.
菲比，過來
I wanna show you something in the bathroom.
我要你看看 浴室裡的一樣東西
Monica, grow up.
摩妮卡，成熟一點
-What's behind your back? -Something I want Phoebe's opinion on.
-你的背後藏了什麼東西？ -我希望菲比能給點意見
-You don't want my opinion? -Not really.
-你不要我的意見？ -我不要
Come on, I'm your older brother. Ask me.
少來了，我是你哥哥 問我吧
Okay, big brother.
好吧，哥哥
Which one would make your best friend want to do your little sister?
你覺得哪一件能讓你朋友 想上你妹妹？
The red one.
紅色那件
Hey.
嘿
I know you're depressed, so I brought someone to cheer you up.
我知道你很沮喪 所以我帶了一個東西來幫你打氣
Right outside is a real, live, furry playmate.
他是真的 毛茸茸的玩物
I'm not sleeping with your friend Jane again.
我不要 再跟你朋友珍上床
Hey, a dog!
是小狗
Who, you gotta admit, looks a lot like Jane.
你得承認 他長得很像珍
He's the happiest dog ever. I borrowed him from my friend Wendy.
他是最快樂的小狗 我跟我朋友溫蒂借了他
So you can keep him till he cheers you up.
你可以留下他 直到你再打起精神來
I borrow him myself from time to time..
我自己常借用他…
when I get depressed thinking about..
只要我心情不好 想到…
world hunger, poverty..
世界饑荒跟貧窮問題…
Not to trivialize your pain.
不是說你的痛苦微不足道
Thanks so much, Pheebs. We are gonna have so much fun!
謝謝你，菲比 我們一定會玩得很開心
Oh, not that kind of fun.
不是那種開心
Happy Valentine's!
情人節快樂
I'm slipping into something a bit less comfortable and a bit more slutty.
我穿上不是很舒服 但是很放蕩的東西
"Candy and Cookie"?
「糖果跟餅乾」？
"Candy and Cookie"?!
Monica got me porn?
摩妮卡幫我租色情片？
Girl-on-girl porn?!
女同志的片子？
She really must love me!
她一定很愛我
-Yeah, just relax. -I love you, St. Valentine.
-好吧，放輕鬆 -我愛你，聖范倫鐵諾
Whoa, whoa, that's not pretty.
那真的不太好看
Now push!
用力推
Oh, God, it hurts!
天啊，好痛
Worst porn ever! Worst porn ever!
這是最難看的色情片 這是最難看的色情片
-Oh, make it stop! -I am trying!
-快停下來 -我在弄了
Get the ball. Ready? Get the ball!
去接球，準備好了嗎？去接球
You're cute, but you're not too smart.
你很可愛，但你不太聰明
Did I just throw this?
我剛丟了這個？
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
I accidentally packed these with my stuff.
我不小心把這些 跟我的東西混在一起
-Who is this? -Phoebe's friend's dog.
-他是誰？ -菲比朋友的狗
I don't know his real name. I call him Mozzarella.
我不知道他叫什麼名字 我叫他莫查利拉起司
You are so cute. I wish I could play, but I've gotta go to work.
你好可愛，我希望能留下來玩 但我得去上班
I hope I stop talking like this before my meeting. Yes, I do.
我希望開會時 我不會這樣說話，對，沒錯
Bye-bye, Joey. Seriously, I can't stop it.
再見，喬伊 說真的，我改不過來
Come here! Hey!
過來
That's Rachel. She used to live here.
她是瑞秋，以前她住在這裡
Might as well be honest with you. We love her.
老實跟你說 我們愛她
But we can't have her.
但我們不能擁有她
I really miss her.
我真的想念她
Hey, you understand, right? You're a guy.
你瞭解吧？ 你是男生
Well, you used to be.
你以前是的
So, what do you think?
你覺得怎樣？
I've still got it.
我還是很辣
-Why did you get me this? -What is it?
-你為什麼要給我這個？ -那是什麼？
It's yelling, bleeding, dilating.
裡面全是尖叫，鮮血跟擴張的陰道
Oh, the dilating!
擴張的陰道
Is this the video of the birth? It's Phoebe's. Why were you watching it?
這是紀錄生產的錄影帶？ 它是菲比的，你為什麼要看它？
I thought maybe you got me porn for Valentine's Day.
我以為或許你會在情人節 幫我租色情片
If you thought I was gonna get you porn for Valentine's Day..
如果你以為我會在情人節 幫你租色情片…
you were right.
那麼你說對了
It's about a girl who moves to the city in search of stardom..
片中的女主角 跑到大都市來追尋星夢…
but ends up having sex with a lot of guys.
最後她跟很多男人 上床
It got four stars.
它有四星級的評價
Wait a minute. Those aren't stars.
等一下，根本沒有那種事
-Anyway, you wanna take a look? -Well..
-總之你要看一下嗎？ -喔…
-I'm not really in a sexy mood. -Hey, what's going on?
-我真的沒心情做愛 -發生了什麼事？
Remember the first time you saw Jaws..
還記得你第一次 看大白鯊…
how long it took to go back in the water?
你花了多少時間 才敢再下水游泳？
We can't let this tape wreck Valentine's Day.
我們不能讓這卷錄影帶 毀了情人節
You gotta get past it.
你得克服它
Just get back on the horse.
重振雄風
Otherwise, the horse is gonna go into the bedroom and change into her sweatpants.
不然我要回房 換上我的運動褲
-Okay, you don't know. You didn't see it. -Childbirth is beautiful.
-好吧，你不知道，你沒有看到它 -生孩子的過程很美
Oh, beautiful? Really?
很美？真的嗎？
You think this is beautiful?
你覺得這很美嗎？
Oh, my God! No wonder my mother hates me!
天啊 難怪我媽恨我
-See, honey, there's.. -Don't touch me!
-甜心… -別碰我
-Hi! -Hey!
-嗨 -嘿
-How was Atlantic City? -Good.
-亞特蘭大好玩嗎？ -很好玩
I brought you back a present.
我幫你買了禮物
You didn't have to..
你不必…
Saltwater taffy?!
鹹水太妃糖？
Thanks.
謝謝
Interestingly, it isn't made with seawater.
有趣的是 它沒有加任何海水
It's actually made with salted fresh water.
事實上 它是用加鹽淡水做的
That's not interesting.
那一點都不有趣
-I think it's interesting. -Me too. I missed you!
-我覺得很有趣 -我也是，我想你
Me too.
我也是
-How was your week? -Good.
-這星期你過得如何？ -非常好
-The baby started kicking. -How exciting!
-寶寶開始會踢人了 -太棒了
It was amazing. The only thing is, I wasn't there the first time.
太神奇了 只不過第一次我並不在場
-Oh, no. -I was missing out on all this stuff.
-不 -我錯過了所有的過程
-Joey suggested Rachel move in with me. -Yeah, right.
-喬伊建議瑞秋搬過來跟我住 -想得美
-What? -Joey cracks me up.
-什麼？ -喬伊害我笑得肚子痛
"Have your ex-wife move in. That wouldn't be awkward."
「讓你的前妻搬進去 那一點也不彆扭」
Imagine, I go away for a few days..
想像我離開了幾天…
and my boyfriend is living with a woman he got pregnant.
我男朋友跟懷了他孩子的女人 住在一起
So, what'd you tell him?
你怎麼跟他說？
You didn't tell Mona Rachel moved in?
你沒有告訴蒙娜 瑞秋搬過去了？
She seemed to think it was such a crazy idea.
她似乎覺得 那是個瘋狂的點子
Plus, she got me taffy.
而且她送我太妃糖
-Really? I've never had any. -Ever?
-真的嗎？我沒吃過太妃糖 -真的？
My mom was too busy planning her suicide to provide saltwater treats.
我媽忙著計劃自殺 沒空買海灘小吃給我
Thank you.
謝謝
Are you gonna tell her?
你要告訴她嗎？
I will. I want to butter her up first.
我想我得先哄哄她
I'm gonna take her to dinner, do all this romantic stuff.
我要帶她去吃晚餐 做一些浪漫的事
When she thinks I'm the best boyfriend ever..
當她覺得 我是有史以來最棒的男朋友時…
I'll tell her my pregnant ex-girlfriend is living with me.
我會告訴她我懷孕的前女友 跟我一起住
If I haven't said it before, she's a lucky, lucky lady.
或許我沒有說過 她是個非常幸運的女人
So where are..? What the crap is up with this stuff?
我們… 這個玩意怎麼了？
Is it gum? Is it food? What's the deal?
它是口香糖嗎？它是食物嗎？ 怎麼了？
Oh, it's nice. May I try a pink one?
好好吃 我能試試粉紅色的嗎？
So I just have to plan the perfect night.
我得計劃 這個完美的夜晚
Hey, what's the best date you ever had?
你最棒的約會經驗 是什麼？
Last year, Greg Hayman took me to a very nice sushi dinner.
去年葛瑞格海曼 帶我去吃很好吃的壽司大餐
Then we took a romantic walk to a nearby research lab..
我們散步 到附近的研究室…
where we trashed the place and freed 20 monkeys.
我們闖進裡面 放走二十隻猴子
I knew it! I knew I wasn't crazy!
我就知道 我就知道我沒有發瘋
Last year, a monkey did attack me at the bus stop!
去年的確有一隻猴子 在公車站攻擊我
So between her and me being friends, and her history with Ross..
她跟我是朋友 她跟羅斯交往過…
it just isn't gonna happen.
這種事絕不能發生
It'd be like you falling in love with a cat.
那就像是 你愛上一隻貓
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
How's my favorite dog, huh? How's my favorite dog?
我最喜歡的狗怎麼了？ 他還好嗎？
You're subdued.
你太壓抑了
-Did you give him a beer? -No.
-你讓他喝啤酒了？ -不
-Will you excuse us? We need to talk. -Sure.
-對不起，我們需要談一談 -當然
Oh, me, right.
我，對
-He's miserable. What happened to him? -Nothing.
-他很難過，他是怎麼了？ -沒事
-We talked about stuff. -What stuff?
-我們聊了一些事 -什麼事？
Rachel stuff.
關於瑞秋的事
Oh, Joey, you bummed him out! This is the happiest dog in the world.
喬伊，你害得他很難過 他是全世界最快樂的狗
He spends a day with you, and look!
他才跟你相處一天，你看
He's breathing.
他還在呼吸
Okay, well, he's watching us so just look happy, okay?
好吧，他在看著我們 表現的快樂一點，好嗎？
-I'll take him to Wendy's. -He's fine.
-我要帶他去溫蒂家 -他很好
Look.
你看
Here's your ball!
快接球
Get your ball! Get your ball!
去接球 去接球
Get..
去…
Of course.
當然
You don't want a tennis ball.
你不要網球
Not when you can have a meatball.
因為你可以吃肉球
Come on, get the meatball.
來吧，去接肉球
God, what have I done to you?
天啊，我對你做了什麼？
I broke the dog, Pheebs! I broke the dog!
我害死那隻狗了，菲比 我把他弄得精神崩潰了
Thanks.
謝謝
I'm going to pick up Mona. What are you doing tonight?
我要去接蒙娜 今晚你要做什麼？
Oh, I got big Valentine's plans.
我有很棒的情人節計劃
I got my Chinese food on the way, and your saltwater taffy.
我訂了中國菜 還有你的鹹水太妃糖
Interestingly, it isn't made with seawater..
真有趣 它沒有加海水…
We actually watched the documentary together.
我們是一起 看那部紀錄片的
Oh, my Chinese food. I'll get my cash.
我的外賣來了 我去拿錢
Mona?
蒙娜
What are..? Hi! How are you?
什麼… 嗨，你好嗎？
I'm supposed to pick you up.
我應該去接你的
I made you a Valentine's dinner. Surprise!
我幫你做了情人節晚餐 大驚喜
-Oh! Hey, Mona! -Hi, Rachel.
-蒙娜 -嗨，瑞秋
What's she doing here?
她在這裡做什麼？
I have no idea.
我不知道
I'll be watching TV if anybody needs me.
如果你們要找我 我在房裡看電視
What is she doing?
她在做什麼？
Lately she just likes hanging out here.
最近 她喜歡待在這裡
-Why? -I think she's lonely.
-為什麼？ -我想她很寂寞
But it's Valentine's Day. Can't we ask her to go?
但今天是情人節 我們能請她離開嗎？
Well, no, she's way too emotional.
不行，她太激動了
And by emotional, I mean crazy!
我是說她瘋了
That's just my Chinese food.
我的外賣來了
She has food delivered here?
她叫外賣送到這裡來？
Yes, she's emotional, but ballsy.
對，她很激動，但她大膽
I'm gonna get in my sweats and eat this in bed.
我要去換運動服 躺在床上吃飯
And you thought she was gonna be in our way!
你還以為 她會妨礙到我們
Open the champagne, and I will be right back.
打開香檳 我馬上回來
-I've got a surprise. -You got another ex-wife back there?
-我有大驚喜 -你另一個前妻也藏在裡面？
Please start drinking.
請開始喝香檳
-I'm just gonna grab the phone. -Rachel, wait.
-我只是要打電話 -瑞秋，等一下
I hope you don't take this the wrong way.
我希望 你不會誤會
-What are you doing? -Do you need the phone?
-你在做什麼？ -你要打電話嗎？
No.
不
Ross is too nice to say it, but this is his apartment.
羅斯太好心了沒辦法說出口 但這是他的公寓
We need boundaries, so why don't you go back to your place.
我們需要隱私 你為什麼不回你家呢？
But, Mona, I live here.
蒙娜，我住在這裡
Happy Valentine's Day!
情人節快樂
Or, something to remember me by.
或者這能讓你在分手後記得我
-How long has it been this time? -Ninety seconds.
-這次是多久？ -九十秒
Ninety seconds is a long time not to think about it.
九十秒沒想到它 真的很久
Except all I did was think about it.
但我滿腦子都是它
I know. It haunts me.
我知道，我也忘不了
Till now, the worst thing I'd seen was my dad doing shots off the houseboy.
在這之前我看過最糟糕的事 是我爸跟服務生上床
After this, I would gladly make that my screen saver.
在這之後我會很樂意 把他們的照片做成屏幕保護程式
We have to get past this. We'll pretend it never existed.
我們得忘了這件事 我們得假裝它不存在
I could do that.
我可以那麼做
Now all we gotta do is get rid of this chair.
我們只需要 丟掉那張椅子
-Oh, thank God! -I know.
-謝天謝地 -我知道
Come in!
請進
Hi. I'm sorry to barge in on your Valentine.
我很抱歉 破壞了你們的情人節
I had to get away from the yelling. Mona's dumping Ross.
我得遠離那些叫罵聲 蒙娜要跟羅斯分手
-Oh, my God. -Poor Ross.
-天啊 -可憐的羅斯
We watch him do yoga in his underwear, but for this he closes the drapes.
我們看過他穿內褲做瑜珈 但這次他更慘
You know that birthing tape you wanted to see?
關於那卷 你想看的生產錄影帶
It's here.
它在這裡
We should warn you before you watch it. Don't watch it.
我們得在你看它之前警告你 千萬別看它
You saw it? Is it scary?
你們看過了？很可怕嗎？
It's ironic how footage of someone being born..
諷刺的是 生孩子的畫面…
can make you want to kill yourself.
讓人想要自殺
Honey, she may not have to watch it but she's going to have to do it.
甜心，她不必看它 但她非生孩子不可
Now I'm all freaked out. Will you watch it with me?
現在我嚇壞了 你們能跟我一起看嗎？
No, but I'll leave a sweater that smells like me right next to you.
不，但我會把有我體味的毛衣 放在你旁邊
Monica, come on. You want to have kids.
摩妮卡，少來了 你想生孩子
I do.
沒錯
But the stork is gonna bring mine.
但送子鳥 會把寶寶送來給我
Seriously, you're not gonna make me watch this alone.
說真的 你們不能逼我一個人看這個
She's right. Of course not.
她說的對，當然不行
Honey, get the tape.
甜心，去拿錄影帶
This reminds me of a very specific part of the tape.
這讓我想起了 錄影帶裡某一段內容
Oh, sure. But if you leave a drumstick under there and you're a bad roommate.
當然，如果你把雞腿放在那裡 你是個爛室友
Here we go.
來吧
Okay.
好吧
Oh, my.
天啊
Come on, come on.
加油
Why is that baby torturing that woman?
為什麼寶寶要折磨那個女人？
Why have I seen this thing three times?
為什麼我要看這個玩意三次？
It's beautiful.
好美
-It's horrible! -I know, I know! I'm so sorry for you!
-好可怕 -我知道，我為你感到難過
What do I do? I don't want to do this! How do I get out of it?
我該怎麼辦？我不要做這個 我要怎麼把寶寶丟掉？
-You guys! You guys, look! -What? Did her ass explode?
-大家快看 -什麼？她的屁股爆炸了嗎？
No, the baby's out. Look.
不，寶寶出來了，你們看
Look at those little fingers and toes.
看看那些小手指跟小腳趾
Look how happy the mom is now.
看看媽媽現在有多高興
-Oh, Rach. -Screw you! You don't have to do it!
-瑞秋 -去你們的，你們不必生小孩
-Hey. -Hey!
-嘿 -嘿
-What's up? -Mona just dumped me.
-怎麼了？ -蒙娜剛剛甩了我
Oh, man, I'm sorry. Why?
天啊，我很遺憾，為什麼？
Lately, I haven't exactly been the perfect boyfriend.
最近我不是 完美男友
I didn't tell her I got Rachel pregnant.
我沒有告訴她 我讓瑞秋懷孕
I gave her a key to my apartment and then had the locks changed.
我給她我家的鑰匙 然後換了鎖
Then I lied to her about Rachel moving in with me.
我騙她 瑞秋搬到我家的事
In a way, I judge her for not breaking up with me sooner.
在某方面 我怪她不早點跟我分手
That really sucks. Especially on Valentine's Day.
那真的很爛 特別是在情人節
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
等一下 你在這裡做什麼？
Joey without a date on Valentine's Day?
喬伊在情人節 沒有約會？
What's going on, huh? Girl trouble?
發生了什麼事？你跟女人有麻煩？
-Sort of. -Really?
-可以那麼說 -真的嗎？
You don't have to seem so happy about it.
你不必表現得這麼高興
Maybe I can help.
或許我能幫忙
Whatever it is, I am sure it has happened to me.
不論發生了什麼事 我相信我也有相同的經驗
You know, actually, once I got dumped during sex.
事實上 我有次在做愛時被甩了
-So anyway, what is it? -Forget about it. It's no big deal.
-到底發生了什麼事？ -算了，沒什麼大不了的
-Come on, what is it? -It's nothing.
-少來了，怎麼了？ -沒事
Hey, it's me. Why can't you tell me?
是我 你為什麼不告訴我？
Okay. Sit down.
好吧，坐下
There's this woman that I like a lot.
我很喜歡一個女人
But it can't happen.
但那是不可能的
She's not a Tribbiani?
她不會是你的姐妹吧？
No!
不
So is she someone from work?
她是你的同事？
Yes.
對
Well, does she like you?
她喜歡你嗎？
Sometimes I think she could.
有時候我覺得是的
But I can't do anything about it.
但我什麼事都不能做
Why not?
為什麼？
It's complicated.
事情很複雜
She was with this other guy for a long time.
她跟另一個男人 交往了很久
Someone from work too.
他也是我的同事
I could never do that to the guy. We're friends.
我沒辦法那樣對他 我們是好朋友
Wait, I thought you hated everyone at work.
等一下 我以為你討厭所有的同事
No, no. I only say that..
不，我會那麼說…
so Chandler won't feel threatened because I'm his only friend.
錢德才不會覺得被威脅了 因為我是他唯一的朋友
Excuse me?
你說什麼？
Sorry, sorry. And I'm your only friend too.
抱歉 我也是你唯一的朋友
So this guy she used to go out with, is he still in love with her?
以前跟她交往過的那個男人 還愛著她嗎？
-No, I don't think so. -Okay.
-我想應該不愛了 -好吧
Is he a good guy?
他是好人嗎？
Yeah, he's the best.
對，他是最棒的
-Then talk to him. -I don't know.
-跟他談一談 -我不知道
It's worth finding out, if you like her.
如果你喜歡她 這值得試一試
I do, so much.
我真的非常喜歡她
I can't stop thinking about her. I can't sleep..
我沒辦法不想到她 我睡不著…
You know what? You have to go for it.
你知道嗎？ 你得盡力去爭取
How often does this happen to you? You owe it to yourself.
你常遇到這種事嗎？ 你應該為自己這麼做的
Here's your warm milk.
你的溫牛奶來了
I'm gonna put the bourbon in it at home.
我要回家 加點波本酒
Anyway, seriously, just talk to the guy, okay?
說真的 跟那個男的談一談，好嗎？
Let me know how it goes.
告訴我結果
It's Rachel.
是瑞秋
You're having a baby and you need to prepare.
你要生孩子了 你得做好準備
You're gonna make yourself watch the whole thing. Just do it!
你得看完整卷錄影帶 看吧
I came to the big city to become a star.
我來到這個大城市 希望成為大明星
-I'll do anything to make that happen. -Anything?
-為了圓夢我任何事都願意做 -任何事？
Maybe it starts with how she gets pregnant.
或許我該從她 怎麼懷孕開始看起
I wonder which one of these guys becomes the father.
不知道哪個男人 是孩子的爸
No, no. Can't get pregnant that way.
不 那樣子是不會懷孕的